{
  "qa": [
    {
      "id": "1",
      "question": "1 + 1 = ",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "id": "2",
      "question": "1 + 3 = ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": "3",
      "question": "1 + 5 = ",
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "id": "4",
      "question": "1 + 7 = ",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "id": "5",
      "question": "1 + 9 = ",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": "6",
      "question": "1 + 11 = ",
      "answer": 12
    },
    { "id": "7", "question": "1 + 13 = ", "answer": 14 },
    {
      "id": "8",
      "question": "1 + 15 = ",
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": "9",
      "question": "1 + 17 = ",
      "answer": 18
    },

    {
      "id": "10",
      "question": "1 + 19 = ",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": "11",
      "question": "1 + 21 = ",
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "id": "12",
      "question": "1 + 23 = ",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": "13",
      "question": "1 + 25 = ",
      "answer": 26
    },
    {
      "id": "14",
      "question": "1 + 27 = ",
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "id": "15",
      "question": "1 + 29 = ",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "id": "16",
      "question": "1 + 31 = ",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "id": "18",
      "question": "2 + 50 = ",
      "answer": 52
    },
    {
      "id": "19",
      "question": "300 + 31 = ",
      "answer": 331
    },
    {
      "id": "20",
      "question": "2 + 57 = ",
      "answer": 59
    },
    {
      "id": "21",
      "question": "18 + 31 = ",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "id": "22",
      "question": "12 + 24 = ",
      "answer": 36
    },
    {
      "id": "23",
      "question": "11 - 31 = ",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": "24",
      "question": "10 / 2 = ",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "id": "25",
      "question": "19 X 1 = ",
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "id": "26",
      "question": "19 - 6 = ",
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": "27",
      "question": "19 - 2 = ",
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "id": "28",
      "question": "13 X 2 = ",
      "answer": 26
    },
    {
      "id": "29",
      "question": "40 - 1 = ",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "id": "30",
      "question": "17 - 5 = ",
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": "31",
      "question": "12 - 1 = ",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "id": "32",
      "question": "4 X 1 = ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": "33",
      "question": "8 / 2 = ",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": "34",
      "question": "1 - 1 = ",
      "answer": 0
    }
  ]
}
